http://www.smipack.it/profilo/smipack-privacy-page

ITENFRESPT
Who we areCompany profileThe new headquarters of SMIPACKKey dataOur missionThe SMI GroupOur historyOur branchesQuality and Environment CertificationsCertifications and AssociationsGovernanceCorporate GovernanceEthical CodeCorporate Social ResponsibilityQuality and Environment PolicyGeneral Data Protection RegulationWhistleblowingProductsPACKAGING TECHNOLOGY OPEN TO EVERYONEL-seal hood packersSL SeriesL-seal hood packersS SeriesL-sealer, automatic L-sealer, shrinking tunnelFP SeriesContinuous automatic sealers with shrink tunnelHS SeriesSemiautomatic and automatic shrinkwrappers with sealing barBP SeriesAutomatic overlap shrinkwrappersXP SeriesWrap-around case packersWPS SeriesAutomatic handle applicatorsHA SeriesServicesAfter sales technical supportSpare partsTraining coursesMedia centerNewsPress ReleasesThey say about usSMIPACKNOW MagazineCase historiesExhibitionsContactsSales and service networkInfo InquiryPrivacy statementCareersCareersSend Your CVEdit your CVJob opportunitiesWho we areCompany profileThe new headquarters of SMIPACKKey dataOur missionThe SMI GroupOur historyOur branchesQuality and Environment CertificationsCertifications and AssociationsGovernanceCorporate GovernanceEthical CodeCorporate Social ResponsibilityQuality and Environment PolicyGeneral Data Protection RegulationWhistleblowingProductsPACKAGING TECHNOLOGY OPEN TO EVERYONEL-seal hood packersSL SeriesL-seal hood packersS SeriesL-sealer, automatic L-sealer, shrinking tunnelFP SeriesContinuous automatic sealers with shrink tunnelHS SeriesSemiautomatic and automatic shrinkwrappers with sealing barBP SeriesAutomatic overlap shrinkwrappersXP SeriesWrap-around case packersWPS SeriesAutomatic handle applicatorsHA SeriesServicesAfter sales technical supportSpare partsTraining coursesMedia centerNewsPress ReleasesThey say about usSMIPACKNOW MagazineCase historiesExhibitionsContactsSales and service networkInfo InquiryPrivacy statementCareersCareersSend Your CVEdit your CVJob opportunities
Privacy statementSales and service networkInfo InquiryPrivacy statement
Share
TRANSPARENCYLawfulness of processingAll activities relating to personal data processing shall be lawful (consent, contract obligations, vital interests of the data subject or of third parties, compliance with legal obligations to which the controller is subject, public interest or exercise of official authority, legitimate interest pursued by the controller or by third parties).Information statementThe information statement has been improved and updated to the new regulations (art. 13 and 14 GDPR).Rights of the data subjects (right of access, right to erasure-right to be forgotten, right to restriction of processing, right to object, right to data portability)Technical and organization measures have been adopted to ensure the data subject's exercise of his rights and to meet the data subject requirements.Controllers, processorsBased on the new principle of “accountability”, SMI Group organization was re-defined, in order to proactively ensure integral compliance with the Regulation.Redefinition of the role of data processors and service suppliers whose activity implies personal data processing.Risk of data processing; accountability measures taken by controllers and processors (Impact assessment, record of processing activities, security of processing, data breach)The “Conformity document”, including records of data processing activity, plans, adopts and demonstrates all technical and organizational measures taken to adequately perform the data processing activities and specifies the necessary procedures to be adopted to notify data breach.Transfer of personal data to international organizationsSmipack adheres to the general principles and guarantees concerning the transfer of personal data to third Countries.Policy on personal data processingThe Controller is:SMIPACK S.p.A.Head office: Via Carlo Ceresa, 10 - 24015 San Giovanni Bianco (BG) ITALYVAT nr: IT02529010163 - R.E.A. 234981For further information, write to: privacy@smigroup.netAccording to the European Regulation 679/2016, the data subject is entitled to exercise the rights set forth in the Regulation.The integral version of art. 15; 16; 17; 18; 20; 21; 77 of the European Regulation is attached to this document.Articles GDPRIn order to exercise your rights, please send the application form duly filled in to the Controller's address.Request to exercise the rights by the data subjectInformation on candidate's personal data processingInformation on suppliers'/agents' personal data processingInformation on customer's personal data processingInformation on personal data processing - newslettersInformation on personal data processing for information requestsCookies policy
Share
Contact us
SMIPACK S.p.A.
Address: Via Piazzalunga, 30 24015 San Giovanni Bianco BG
Italy
Phone: +39 0345 40.400
E-mail: info.smipack@smigroup.net
Monday - Friday: 08:00 - 12:00 / 13:30 - 17:30Saturday - Sunday: Closed
Newsletter
.
Subscribe
© SMIPACK S.p.A. 2020
Privacy statement - Legal notice
×Close Privacy statement
TRANSPARENCYLawfulness of processingAll activities relating to personal data processing shall be lawful (consent, contract obligations, vital interests of the data subject or of third parties, compliance with legal obligations to which the controller is subject, public interest or exercise of official authority, legitimate interest pursued by the controller or by third parties).Information statementThe information statement has been improved and updated to the new regulations (art. 13 and 14 GDPR).Rights of the data subjects (right of access, right to erasure-right to be forgotten, right to restriction of processing, right to object, right to data portability)Technical and organization measures have been adopted to ensure the data subject's exercise of his rights and to meet the data subject requirements.Controllers, processorsBased on the new principle of “accountability”, SMI Group organization was re-defined, in order to proactively ensure integral compliance with the Regulation.Redefinition of the role of data processors and service suppliers whose activity implies personal data processing.Risk of data processing; accountability measures taken by controllers and processors (Impact assessment, record of processing activities, security of processing, data breach)The “Conformity document”, including records of data processing activity, plans, adopts and demonstrates all technical and organizational measures taken to adequately perform the data processing activities and specifies the necessary procedures to be adopted to notify data breach.Transfer of personal data to international organizationsSmipack adheres to the general principles and guarantees concerning the transfer of personal data to third Countries.Policy on personal data processingThe Controller is:SMIPACK S.p.A.Head office: Via Carlo Ceresa, 10 - 24015 San Giovanni Bianco (BG) ITALYVAT nr: IT02529010163 - R.E.A. 234981For further information, write to: privacy@smigroup.netAccording to the European Regulation 679/2016, the data subject is entitled to exercise the rights set forth in the Regulation.The integral version of art. 15; 16; 17; 18; 20; 21; 77 of the European Regulation is attached to this document.Articles GDPRIn order to exercise your rights, please send the application form duly filled in to the Controller's address.Request to exercise the rights by the data subjectInformation on candidate's personal data processingInformation on suppliers'/agents' personal data processingInformation on customer's personal data processingInformation on personal data processing - newslettersInformation on personal data processing for information requestsCookies policy
Close
×Close Legal notice
SMIPACK S.p.A.Sede amministrativa: Via Carlo Ceresa, 10 24015 San Giovanni Bianco (BG) ITALIASede legale: Via Monte Grappa, 7 - 24121 Bergamo (BG) - ITALIAC.F. e P. IVA IT02529010163 - R.E.A. 234981Capitale Sociale Euro 5.000.000 i.v.
Close
